this.cm 2016-04-24

# Privacy | This.

_Last updated: October 2015_

This Privacy Policy covers what This. Media Co. (“This.,” “we” or “our”) does with the Personal Information (as defined herein) that you share with us and the data we collect when you are accessing our Service. Personal Information about our users is an integral part of our business, so please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using or accessing our Service, you agree to the privacy policies outlined below. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings provided in our Terms of Service.

## What Does this Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of Personal Information that This. collects while you are using the Site and the Service. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that This. does not own or control, including but not limited to third party services you access through This., or to individuals that This. does not employ or manage. As our Service integrates with third-party sites, such as Facebook, Twitter, and other sites and social networks, we assume that you are already aware of the privacy policies of those other sites and networks when using This. and when you allow This. to interact with these sites and networks on your behalf.

## What This. Collects and Shares About You

By visiting and interacting with This. or its Service, you provide us with three types of information: Personally Identifiable Information (i.e., information that you purposely disclose or that you authorize to be disclosed on your behalf); User Contributed Content; and Automatic Information (e.g. your IP address and browser type). Personally Identifiable Information, User Contributed Content, and Automatic Information are collectively referred to herein as “Personal Information.” Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, the following:

## Personally Identifiable Information

“Personally Identifiable Information” may include, without limitation, information provided when you register for the Service, including your name; phone number; email address; occupation; employer; gender; age; birthday; Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, and/or other social network usernames, ‘likes’, preferences, and number of friends you have via social networks; use information regarding your use of the Service; profile picture; and browser information. The Personally Identifiable Information you provide is used for such purposes as: allowing you to set up a user account and profile that can be used to interact with other users and your followers through the Service; providing, maintaining, and improving our Service and the content thereof; to better understand how you interact with This.; providing personalized features of the Service; communicating with you about new features; providing metrics and feedback to potential and existing customers; satisfying customer and user needs; monitoring your use and aggregate users’ use of This.; administering your inquiries; and enforcing our (or our partners’ or users’) rights. We also use your Personal Information to deliver custom content and advertising that may be of interest to you. If you connect via This. to a third-party website (e.g., using Facebook connect), This. will receive and might store any information that is made available by such third-party website. If you contact us by email, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence and will use your email and correspondence if we respond to you.

## User Contributed Content

The key functionality of This. is to provide a social networking platform where you can find and share the best entertainment, art and journalism on the web; follow the people you trust; give thanks for their links and share the links you love (collectively, the “Service”). This includes sharing links to this entertainment, art and journalism which requires creating or uploading different kinds of content to the Site, including text, messages, posts, html, URLs, pictures, video and other forms of content (collectively, “User Contributed Content”). As you upload User Contributed Content you should be mindful of your privacy as well as the privacy of others. The User Contributed Content that you upload and post will be collected and retained.

## Automatic Information

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. This. may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, This. cookie information, and the information you request. This. may use this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the Site and the Service. We may also automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of users of our Site and Service and their components. This. may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data may enable us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Site and the Service, so we can make the Site and the Service appealing to as many users as possible. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information, not information about you personally, to our partners about how our users, collectively, use our Site and the Service.

## Use of Personal Information by Followers and the Public

  * Followers: Your followers can see, for example, the User Contributed Content that you have uploaded to the Site. Individuals reading this information may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in your User Contributed Content or other content that you create in the Service.
  * Publicly Available Information: When you use our Service, certain information is public, such as your public user profile information, thanks, links you have shared, public photos, and lists of followers, and may be shared with or disclosed to third parties.

## Use of Related Personal Information in Connection with Third Parties and Our Partners

To protect your privacy, we limit the sharing of Personally Identifiable Information with third parties. We conduct our business with great respect for the confidential nature of the information being provided. We will not share information about you except as outlined below.

We do not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose non-public information about you with such third parties that is likely to uniquely identify or locate any individual or entity to any unaffiliated third party for any reason, except as noted below:

  * We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client to access your This. account.
  * Where such disclosure is required or appropriate pursuant to laws or securities regulations, including cooperating with government agencies, other regulatory bodies and law enforcement officials, performing background checks, resolving disputes or performing risk-management functions.
  * To help us improve our services to you, we may engage another business to help us to carry out certain internal functions such as account processing, client services or other data collection relevant to our business. We may also provide a party with client information from our databases to help us analyze and identify client needs or to notify clients of particular services offerings. Use of the information shared is strictly limited to the performance of the task we request and used for no other purpose.
  * As mentioned above, we may share aggregate information about our users, such as the number of users who used a particular service, which would include as a part thereof your personal information with our partners. We do not have any control over, and are not responsible for, our partner’s use of this information.
  * We may share information with non-financial companies that perform services for us, such as companies that perform credit card processing services on our behalf.
  * We may share information with affiliates if the information is required to provide the services you requested. An affiliate is a company that we own or control, or with which there is common ownership with us.
  * We may also disclose your information as necessary to credit reporting or collection agencies, or when necessary to protect our rights or property.
  * While your Personally Identifiable Information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.
  * In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

## Communicating with Our Partners, if Any

From time to time you may choose to share information with our partners, if any, independently from us. Please note that with respect to any information which you choose to share directly with third parties, whether or not you have initially come across such third party through our Service, such information shall not be governed by the terms of this Privacy Policy and shall instead be governed by the privacy policy of such third party, if any. We disclaim any responsibility or liability arising from any information that you share with any third party.

## Our Privacy Policy Does Not Apply to the Sites, if Any, to Which We Link

We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of sites we link to, if any, and we have no control of the use or protection of information provided by you or collected by those sites. Whenever you elect to hyperlink to a linked website, you may be asked to provide registration or other information. Please note that the information you are providing is going to a third party, and you should familiarize yourself with the privacy policy provided by that third party.

## Transference of Services

If This. or its assets are acquired, member information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party.

## Children’s Privacy

This. does not direct its Service at children under 13 years of age, and the Service is not intended to be viewed or used by them. Pursuant to the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) in the United States, This. will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without first obtaining parental consent, and to the extent such information is inadvertently collected, This. will make every commercially reasonable effort to obtain permission from the child’s parent and/or permanently delete the information once it has actual knowledge of such collection. Children should always get permission from their parents before providing any information about themselves (including without limitation first and last names, home addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers and dates of birth) to others, whether via the Internet or any other means.

## Government Requests for Information

We may notify affected users of any emergency government or law enforcement requests for their account information, however, we are not required to do so and may, in fact, be precluded from doing so by applicable law. Furthermore, we may disclose account information to a government agency or law enforcement in response to a valid emergency disclosure request. In connection with any such request, we will require that any such law enforcement or government agency comply with basic principles of free expression, clearly state the legal reason for ascertaining the requested information, and respect the security and infrastructure of the Site by not building any security kinks into our backend. This. will evaluate all emergency disclosure requests on a case-by-case basis in compliance with relevant law. Furthermore, if This. receives information that provides us with a good faith belief that there is an exigent emergency involving the danger of death or serious physical injury to a person, we may provide information necessary to prevent that harm, if we have it. We may not comply with requests for a variety of reasons, including, but not limited to, a request that fails to identify a This. account or a request that is overly broad, in which case we may seek to narrow that request. This. will comply with all applicable laws regarding any government or emergency request for information.

## How Do I Delete My Account?

Should you ever decide to delete your This. account, you may do so by emailing administrator@this.cm. If you terminate your account, your profile and all User Contributed Content will be deleted from our servers; provided, however, that such deletion may not be immediate, and residual copies of your profile information, posts, or comments may remain on backup media for a reasonable period of time. Furthermore, copies of deleted information may remain viewable elsewhere, to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users.

## Updates

We may change and update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and you should regularly check the Site for the most up-to-date version. Should you have any questions regarding the content, please feel free to contact us at administrator@this.cm.
